reigning O
Joseph I-PER
ended O
1-2 O
Raichev I-PER
committed O
Luxembourg I-ORG
five O
point O
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ I-PER
AUGUST O
Nations I-ORG
the I-ORG
League I-MISC
Stephanie I-PER
Vaduz I-LOC
Aggregate O
sources O
145 O
suffered O
BP O
asking O
Treaty I-ORG
Goldman I-PER
ND I-ORG
miles O
sure O
Bill I-MISC
W. I-ORG
hostage O
Commission I-MISC
common O
Morocco I-LOC
Miami I-ORG
Its O
rupees O
Lloyd I-ORG
championship O
books O
later O
League I-ORG
Americans I-MISC
Santos I-PER
track O
family O
accuses O
issued O
Washington I-ORG
democracy I-ORG
University O
Atherton I-PER
fine O
Bonn I-LOC
Organisation I-ORG
around O
Grand I-MISC
knee O
moisture O
PM O
Public O
violent O
Tony I-PER
little O
united O
violation O
Slovakia I-LOC
questions O
started O
Soviet I-MISC
weaker O
shares O
build O
believes O
Pakistan I-ORG
edged O
16 O
buy O
Capital O
Newcombe I-PER
arrives O
Despite O
Nestor I-PER
Officials O
bring O
NBH I-ORG
fact O
disappointing O
Nigerian I-MISC
controls O
offset O
Valletta I-LOC
Iran I-LOC
ITALIAN I-MISC
copper O
Service I-ORG
gathered O
pursue O
Leduc I-LOC
cuts O
row O
seemed O
International I-MISC
general O
injured O
congress O
Commercial I-ORG
Bombay I-MISC
sides O
action O
replaced O
ceremony O
release O
England I-ORG
Davis I-PER
AKRON I-LOC
However O
caused O
climbed O
phase O
63 O
Former O
flight O
Cup I-MISC
Germany I-LOC
Colombo I-LOC
OFFICIAL O
copies O
her O
Justin I-PER
opportunity O
Estonia I-LOC
remain O
Rights I-ORG
saw O
.543 O
.457 O
outlook O
Elect I-ORG
search O
bottom O
WELLINGTON I-LOC
an O
stabbed O
7-4 O
Poland I-PER
various O
average O
meeting O
council O
armed O
Squad O
General I-MISC
Antonio I-PER
Five I-MISC
sought O
LONDON I-LOC
ruling O
73 O
Service O
national O
reach O
Philip I-ORG
Jordan I-LOC
Rating O
Henry I-PER
using O
Elena I-PER
visit O
Freeman I-PER
anything O
set O
staff O
Moenchengladbach I-ORG
Both O
convention O
southern O
Super I-ORG
shooting O
Jerusalem I-ORG
Florence I-LOC
trillion O
NATO I-ORG
proposed O
Atletico I-ORG
customs O
Australian I-MISC
Games I-MISC
broke O
Singer I-MISC
Davis B-MISC
12th I-MISC
Toshiba I-MISC
unnamed O
April O
Fred I-PER
School I-LOC
SOUTH I-LOC
Vale I-ORG
inquiry O
document O
Juan I-PER
is I-ORG
Total I-ORG
U.S.-led I-MISC
Wheat O
customers O
rounds O
Dundee I-PER
Veldman I-PER
Poland I-MISC
data O
drivers O
estimates O
Brad I-PER
shr O
Championship O
Nottingham I-LOC
removed O
fix O
joint O
animals O
challenge O
suspension O
110 O
troubled O
Arthur I-LOC
hat-trick O
fought O
Bruguera I-PER
Central O
Benfica I-ORG
Islamic I-LOC
believed O
down O
Francisco I-PER
AT O
Internet I-MISC
magazine O
innings O
TORONTO I-ORG
British I-ORG
involved O
Sierra I-MISC
BP I-ORG
ST I-ORG
Sion I-PER
medals O
platform O
Flower I-PER
Labour I-MISC
Sakai I-LOC
controversial O
24 O
Scotland I-LOC
powers O
Betaseron I-MISC
O'Neill I-PER
Swiss I-MISC
President I-MISC
Calcutta I-LOC
USA I-LOC
management O
3,000 O
Tirana I-LOC
Roman B-MISC
Kornblum I-PER
South I-ORG
Baltimore I-LOC
investments O
prefix O
_other_ I-LOC
four O
Diego I-LOC
Robert I-PER
markka O
Jordanian I-MISC
Grimsby I-ORG
delivery O
City I-ORG
prevent O
surprise O
central O
Commonwealth I-LOC
homes O
that O
Zealand I-ORG
4 O
. I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
Charles I-PER
reform O
Agassi I-PER
Swedish I-MISC
15. O
cancelled O
's I-ORG
fired O
limits O
shelling O
class O
150 O
GTR I-MISC
Stock I-ORG
Monde I-ORG
Chicago I-LOC
pounds O
Columbia I-ORG
epidemic O
. I-MISC
care O
diesel O
speech O
Ecuador I-LOC
rate O
PTT I-ORG
Radio O
returning O
Villa I-PER
Bristol I-ORG
Santos I-ORG
voters O
Silva I-PER
eight O
Company O
Istanbul I-LOC
Takemura I-PER
unbeaten O
avoid O
Greens I-ORG
* O
longer O
rises O
Nigeria I-LOC
Catholic I-ORG
Doncaster I-ORG
Tamil I-ORG
award O
ranking O
office I-ORG
Hanwha I-ORG
Lawrie I-PER
Rabobank I-ORG
missionaries O
PITTSBURGH I-ORG
Cash O
mines O
326 O
Derek I-PER
Workers O
2.6 O
levels O
26th O
Stefan I-PER
1990 O
though O
kg O
Haj I-PER
March O
1996 I-MISC
agents O
Law I-ORG
55 O
Mitsubishi I-ORG
connection O
Heerenveen I-ORG
W O
Diana I-PER
or O
3/4 O
free O
GKS I-ORG
five-year O
Home O
regular O
2,000 O
probably O
8. O
employees O
Federal O
Pirates I-PER
convicted O
plans O
Toronto I-PER
GAMES O
Kiev I-ORG
A I-MISC
escape O
Colorado I-LOC
limit O
something O
Bremen I-LOC
West I-MISC
audience O
alliance I-ORG
first-half O
thing O
director O
DIGEST O
justice O
Heathrow I-LOC
inflation O
lawsuit O
blast O
Briton I-MISC
Petra I-PER
CSU I-ORG
Antwerp I-ORG
Wall I-LOC
sheet O
BRASILIA I-LOC
placed O
UP O
& I-ORG
Palestinian I-ORG
Eritrea I-LOC
Public I-ORG
Gianluca I-PER
Nyva I-ORG
scoring O
am I-ORG
Brugge I-ORG
Kansas I-LOC
30th O
sign O
scoreless O
Information I-ORG
Cork I-PER
accident O
S&P I-MISC
Baker I-ORG
38th O
Alex I-PER
Honda I-ORG
jail O
century O
Fleurian I-PER
mad O
CITY I-ORG
BY O
RKC I-ORG
brief O
standings O
pay O
same O
lead O
CNIEC I-ORG
excellent O
Among O
renegade O
necessary O
accusing O
SAN I-ORG
1-106 O
increased O
army O
Owens I-PER
shut O
NZ I-ORG
wickets O
Alain I-PER
Freiburg I-LOC
peace O
Kankkunen I-PER
Miguel I-PER
Atlanta I-MISC
denied O
MDS I-ORG
Add I-ORG
Bordeaux I-LOC
University I-LOC
This O
Duisburg I-ORG
likely O
SCOREBOARD O
Anwar I-PER
YORK I-ORG
favour O
Barcelona I-LOC
Volendam I-LOC
heading O
confessed O
Liberation I-ORG
merger O
Jeff I-PER
Gas O
CHICAGO I-ORG
shift O
Bulgaria I-ORG
Attendance O
Pot I-PER
Sweden I-LOC
supporting O
forward O
Belgrade I-LOC
Salomon I-ORG
days O
grenades O
revenue O
TEXAS I-ORG
3.8 O
Socialist I-ORG
Liu I-ORG
aged O
conditions O
Warrington I-ORG
Czech I-ORG
Venezuela I-LOC
Kevorkian I-PER
Florida I-LOC
freed O
air O
Jack I-PER
rose O
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ I-MISC
delay O
debut O
BEAT O
Arnhem I-ORG
SBC I-ORG
provincial O
damage O
survey O
officers O
de I-ORG
Indonesia I-ORG
12 O
Commodities I-ORG
appears O
6 O
Montpellier I-ORG
weekend O
thousands O
struck O
Benetton I-ORG
Charleroi I-LOC
Taiwan I-LOC
poor O
ATLANTA I-LOC
2-6 O
Pollock I-PER
1996-08-30 O
Gloria I-ORG
Lance I-PER
Sakigake I-ORG
NEW I-ORG
Hapoel I-ORG
Division O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kenny I-PER
Calif. I-LOC
96 O
relay O
program I-MISC
Fogarty I-PER
Daily I-ORG
Rome I-LOC
Pakistan I-LOC
4221 O
surrounded O
Rio I-LOC
Greece I-LOC
hospital O
Collinelli I-PER
Arnold I-PER
Field I-PER
An I-PER
Our I-LOC
Taipei I-ORG
Close O
settled O
domestic O
Padres I-ORG
Basque I-ORG
imprisonment O
heroin O
loss O
seeking O
Rica I-LOC
Abu I-LOC
contract O
lot O
Taiwan I-ORG
Lille I-ORG
project O
Everton I-ORG
francs O
hit O
South I-LOC
adding O
senior O
finish O
Mitsubishi I-MISC
rivals O
Berlin I-LOC
equivalent O
6-3 O
Edouard I-MISC
us O
MINNESOTA I-ORG
front O
Oval I-LOC
taka O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
northwest O
Korea I-LOC
Venezuela I-ORG
intends O
Centre I-ORG
whether O
Democrats I-ORG
addition O
versus O
5000 O
sprint O
them O
question O
Olsza I-PER
season O
Stoltenberg I-PER
considered O
Five O
remarkable O
Exchange I-ORG
Rugby O
cannabis O
be O
nothing O
Oklahoma I-MISC
dozens O
regime O
trip O
costs O
Company I-ORG
Rating I-ORG
records O
+44 O
Toronto I-LOC
homered O
nation O
starter O
Delhi I-LOC
suffering O
45 O
option O
semifinal O
Investors O
Larnaca I-LOC
Ieng I-PER
plus O
sport O
weight O
News I-MISC
lows O
conducted O
African I-ORG
recent O
NEW I-LOC
authorities O
streets O
bases O
partners O
Morris I-ORG
factory O
Cozma I-PER
midday O
Nottinghamshire I-ORG
Finland I-ORG
Tibet I-LOC
franc O
someone O
RESULTS O
German I-MISC
reserve O
draw O
1996-08-29 O
Aoki I-PER
professional O
will O
HK$ I-MISC
moving O
Fernando I-PER
Utrecht I-ORG
above O
CHAMPIONSHIP O
seed O
51 O
150 I-MISC
forcing O
An O
himself O
intervention O
leftist O
Queens I-ORG
sold O
East B-MISC
Daniel I-PER
Championship I-MISC
Japanese I-ORG
leave O
Commission I-ORG
blood O
settle O
Notts I-ORG
2. O
Home I-LOC
Petroleum I-MISC
reasons O
Gold I-ORG
alone O
EU I-ORG
Income O
extradition O
YR O
economic O
( I-ORG
Swindon I-ORG
Iraqi I-ORG
time O
imported O
crew O
eye O
East O
than O
claims O
registrations O
Hospital I-LOC
My O
Williams I-PER
Ireland I-ORG
forest O
catch O
reply O
eating O
Croatia I-LOC
chairman O
Brewers I-ORG
veterinary O
drop O
Anderson I-PER
Portuguese I-MISC
basis O
training O
shots O
Mauritius I-LOC
slipped O
agency O
Dealers O
manufacturers O
BOGOTA I-LOC
MONTREAL I-LOC
Donovan I-PER
Congress I-MISC
Stirling I-ORG
approach O
made O
Ripken I-PER
really O
Yellow O
Cyprien I-PER
M. I-PER
feet O
Tennis I-LOC
investigators O
lunch O
fallen O
hear O
Beijing I-LOC
pipes O
resulted O
BOJ I-ORG
for I-ORG
5 O
Ocean I-LOC
store O
Norman I-PER
of I-MISC
Cambridge I-LOC
out O
corn O
ministry I-ORG
ancient O
May O
plane O
Stadler I-PER
whom O
Tottenham I-ORG
retired O
Bangladesh I-LOC
1994 O
100 O
party I-ORG
old O
talking O
presence O
Ethiopia I-LOC
trade O
Damm I-PER
Republic I-MISC
Northamptonshire I-ORG
ratio O
films O
Africa I-LOC
Trinidad I-LOC
August O
Van I-PER
Robert I-ORG
Argentina I-LOC
scheduled O
Bradford I-ORG
retail O
El I-LOC
pursuit O
resort O
clashes O
neighbouring O
loan O
cannot O
abortion O
pain O
202 O
hopes O
accept O
during O
American I-ORG
59 O
facing O
captain O
Windows I-PER
Brian I-PER
interior I-ORG
often O
Defence I-ORG
Melbourne I-ORG
De I-PER
block O
kms O
sex O
detained O
cutting O
skull O
Philippoussis I-PER
worked O
grade O
edition O
Morris I-PER
Barrick I-ORG
Red I-LOC
Jose I-PER
secretary O
Aires I-LOC
MOSCOW I-LOC
Yoshikawa I-PER
top O
THE I-ORG
Law I-MISC
Trade I-ORG
X O
original O
operate O
went O
Wroclaw I-LOC
bit O
Cash I-PER
Krajicek I-PER
MATCH O
Kashmir I-LOC
holding O
arrested O
Western I-MISC
Workers I-ORG
station O
Karachi I-ORG
three-run O
administrative O
70 O
31 O
demonstrators O
Warwickshire I-ORG
bill O
100,000 O
mistakes O
positions O
Costantino I-PER
Council O
owner O
shipments O
Football I-MISC
Mark I-PER
alliance O
Austria I-ORG
maybe O
sound O
1990 I-MISC
Miss I-MISC
event O
Gabon I-LOC
Western I-ORG
tight O
related O
Oklahoma I-ORG
problems O
You O
N O
Authority I-ORG
treaty O
metal O
Smicer I-PER
MADRID I-LOC
de I-MISC
108 O
Prix I-MISC
affected O
Tilburg I-ORG
conflict O
Kingdom I-PER
Jens I-PER
supplies O
Paulo I-LOC
PAKISTAN I-LOC
tell O
speaker O
of O
annual O
restaurant O
soon O
Nov O
We O
targets O
Diego I-PER
a.m. O
Libya I-LOC
East I-LOC
dismissed O
rebels O
41 O
incidents O
who O
Chinese I-MISC
amid O
wait O
Durham I-PER
Names I-ORG
Marcus I-PER
MILWAUKEE I-ORG
Association I-MISC
international O
ST O
speak O
batsman O
19 O
Hendrix I-PER
orders O
Tokyo I-LOC
Mary I-PER
fell O
852 O
verified O
1989 O
Community I-MISC
give O
nominee O
wrist O
winner O
Johnson I-ORG
do I-ORG
profit O
ethnic O
Niugini I-ORG
continue O
Warsaw I-LOC
Old I-LOC
provided O
212 O
summer O
establishment O
Juventus I-ORG
Darren I-PER
HRW O
pending O
marks O
Advanced I-ORG
scientists O
F I-MISC
416 O
led O
Lebanon I-ORG
Chorzow I-ORG
25,000 O
ousted O
flown O
living O
White O
anyone O
speaking O
Julie I-PER
BELGIAN I-MISC
traders O
organisers O
approved O
A O
experience O
------------------------ O
self-rule I-ORG
Germain I-ORG
LTTE I-ORG
DUTCH I-MISC
500 O
AIRES I-LOC
AOL I-ORG
military O
main O
n.a O
Habsudova I-PER
sets O
RALLYING O
. O
controllers O
here O
Massachusetts I-LOC
source O
Regulation I-MISC
case O
2-2 O
( I-PER
St. I-ORG
Paulo I-ORG
Mariners I-ORG
solo O
walks O
confiscated O
Sussex I-ORG
crisis O
A-rated O
arm O
CVG I-ORG
Mia I-PER
7 O
set-top O
_allCaps_ O
29 O
Court I-LOC
Cardiff I-ORG
bush O
Kafelnikov I-PER
kick O
assistant O
love O
President O
NEW O
States I-MISC
Cologne I-ORG
port O
Anke I-PER
War I-ORG
legs O
scientific O
falls O
Lindsay I-PER
called O
BEIJING I-LOC
6-7 O
take O
vice O
Teutenberg I-PER
Final O
WITH O
Dennis I-PER
parties O
turned O
rugby O
Tamil I-LOC
round O
North I-ORG
Barbara I-PER
Indonesia I-LOC
Results O
aid O
49 O
compatriot O
ANKARA I-LOC
container O
, I-LOC
presidential O
RESULT O
KOREAN I-MISC
operating O
identified O
Battle I-ORG
restored O
built O
rankings O
customer O
Brussels I-MISC
commercial O
Republican I-ORG
Shimon I-PER
Year O
Kuwait I-LOC
Interpol I-ORG
felt O
Medical I-ORG
secured O
Moscow I-LOC
Wolverhampton I-ORG
ahead O
Kabariti I-PER
father O
arrests O
process O
request O
Super B-MISC
Eindhoven I-LOC
Edberg I-PER
MANCHESTER I-ORG
Lincoln I-LOC
want O
Serbia I-LOC
firms O
ARA O
Montreal I-LOC
NATIONS I-MISC
Bobby I-PER
handed O
Amount O
withdrew O
applications O
such O
island O
stations O
Daily O
Goldman I-ORG
reports O
League O
concerned O
Bonds I-PER
political O
21 O
Federation I-ORG
542 O
599 O
No I-LOC
riders O
.531 O
Newsdesk I-ORG
Finland I-LOC
legislature O
Bhutto I-PER
Telekom I-ORG
prospects O
barley O
judge O
hard O
Guingamp I-ORG
plants O
prosecutor O
Le I-PER
Peres I-PER
repeat O
advice O
compromise O
7-1 O
threats O
speculation O
compared O
Arantxa I-PER
barred O
left O
Roman I-PER
low O
preparing O
Gas I-ORG
Poland I-LOC
quarter-finals O
dispute O
struggle O
registered O
ANGELES I-ORG
cause O
Moslem I-MISC
complex O
Yamaha I-ORG
read O
Kingdom I-LOC
Andy I-PER
network O
Akron I-LOC
Paulo I-PER
mutual O
fear O
Reserve I-ORG
game O
Airways I-ORG
however O
democracy O
Pioline I-PER
tonnes O
financial O
Simitis I-PER
town O
Interior O
tunnel O
AS I-ORG
million O
ballot O
Finance O
used O
develop O
emergency O
Promodes I-ORG
Diego I-ORG
1.5 O
ANGELES I-LOC
76 O
erupted O
S. I-MISC
35 O
clash O
public O
Russians I-MISC
suspicion O
SOCCER O
Hospital I-PER
Charlton I-PER
men O
Sunday I-PER
War O
insistence O
Reagan I-PER
crowd O
terrorist O
Angolan I-MISC
swimming O
Tsang I-PER
fall O
recovered O
Hakkinen I-PER
4-1 O
call O
county O
surgeon O
Simpson I-PER
losing O
Most B-MISC
Scoreboard O
their O
realised O
He O
close O
slaughter O
Windows I-MISC
Our O
Central I-MISC
Paris I-LOC
Turnover O
8-6 O
Ross I-ORG
investigations O
flew O
Research I-ORG
change O
Team O
lbw O
black O
installed O
CHICAGO I-LOC
Els I-PER
80 O
site O
Angeles I-LOC
To O
Press O
currently O
sea O
ends O
86th O
except O
price O
division O
Norwegian I-MISC
Ducati I-ORG
Four O
162 I-MISC
member O
difficult O
Arab I-LOC
Nicaragua I-LOC
Fastest O
major-league O
games O
invited O
gave O
Doetinchem I-LOC
Although O
asylum O
15-8 O
largely O
girl O
Taylor I-ORG
enter O
Lynch I-PER
cast O
current O
The O
insisted O
served O
Municipal I-ORG
highest O
stadium O
RUGBY O
Francisco I-ORG
taxes O
Marseille I-ORG
Middlesex I-ORG
Campbell I-PER
back O
Baseball O
substantial O
players O
68 O
Stock I-MISC
defends O
Kurdish I-MISC
MILAN I-LOC
Northampton I-LOC
casualties O
since O
Palestinians I-MISC
C. I-PER
therapy O
been O
conference O
Bosnia I-LOC
Costa I-LOC
Zabrze I-ORG
racing O
Midwest I-LOC
Strang I-PER
Community I-ORG
Colombian I-MISC
Mother I-PER
hundreds O
fined O
Tennis I-MISC
beaten O
committee O
included O
Wimbledon I-LOC
research O
Exchange I-MISC
NOTE O
VfB I-ORG
way O
SECOND O
Year I-MISC
Wang I-PER
barrels O
autonomy O
Ten I-MISC
1998 O
SQUAD O
baht O
seized O
settlement O
Larry I-PER
Salang I-LOC
170 O
Turner I-PER
Parma I-ORG
quoted O
West O
Nice I-ORG
JavaSoft I-ORG
Mushtaq I-PER
rubber O
Desk I-ORG
Latest O
arrest O
Western I-LOC
began O
produce O
could O
Humenne I-ORG
Premier O
goalkeeper O
pact O
detective O
division I-ORG
earnings O
Spain I-LOC
Iliescu I-PER
Crystal I-ORG
Pro O
whose O
amount O
Army I-ORG
Eales I-PER
Malik I-PER
officer O
ranked O
Men I-MISC
Bernard I-PER
Georgia I-LOC
solution O
companies O
require O
88 O
photographs O
occurred O
Oliver I-PER
Inzamam-ul-Haq I-PER
Old I-ORG
democratic O
Bucharest I-ORG
next O
Jacques I-PER
workers O
away O
Odra I-ORG
autumn O
central I-ORG
13. O
experts O
got O
this O
California I-LOC
15 O
Jean I-PER
seeding O
half O
UK I-LOC
normal O
refined O
Charleroi I-ORG
Air I-MISC
Gaza I-LOC
ISS O
Scottish I-MISC
technical O
global O
IN O
Microsoft I-ORG
unrest O
month O
together O
events O
offers O
Spring O
development O
charges O
Lincoln I-ORG
60 O
Azharuddin I-PER
rice O
Preston I-PER
MONTREAL I-ORG
became O
hand O
Ekeus I-PER
United I-LOC
Trent I-LOC
Dimitris I-PER
Canada I-LOC
** O
sales O
Net I-ORG
_allCaps_ I-LOC
504 O
welfare O
Black I-MISC
Minister O
well O
Perot I-PER
TIMES I-ORG
complete O
sharp O
Newsroom I-ORG
St. I-LOC
Kong I-ORG
apiece O
Lloyd I-PER
Cyprus I-LOC
Democratic I-ORG
Foreign I-ORG
Volkova I-PER
weapons O
am O
certain O
Ramallah I-LOC
initially O
unions O
Israel B-LOC
B O
7-5 O
Kurds I-MISC
Europe I-ORG
C$ I-MISC
service O
72 O
Mozambique I-LOC
direct O
Greece I-ORG
can O
banks O
Samsung I-ORG
Hogg I-PER
N.J. I-PER
school O
rival O
Wednesday O
launched O
takes O
Hope I-PER
Indian I-MISC
Football I-ORG
CALL O
Munich I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG
attacked O
SEP O
Bundesliga I-MISC
normally O
services O
leading O
21st O
8 O
dealing O
Baseball I-MISC
coach O
12.0 O
Brussels I-LOC
based O
Air O
exports O
earned O
Foe I-PER
-- O
Arkansas I-ORG
SCOTTISH I-MISC
NATIONAL I-MISC
Bowling O
decide O
provide O
dangerous O
observers O
BASKETBALL O
mountain O
521-8 O
Miguel I-ORG
Gooch I-PER
Healy I-PER
Nigeria I-ORG
reluctant O
111 O
Affairs I-ORG
Bogra I-LOC
Georgia I-ORG
Turner I-LOC
building O
Nick I-PER
following O
BOSTON I-LOC
offices O
Note O
name O
stages O
Roe I-PER
Reef I-LOC
between O
In I-ORG
Bosnian I-MISC
elected O
items O
daughter O
A$ I-MISC
Itar-Tass I-ORG
Airbus I-MISC
Ronald I-PER
Buenos I-ORG
Mexico I-LOC
adopted O
ATHLETICS O
25 O
Investors I-ORG
mother O
IMED I-ORG
provinces O
respect O
slow O
Croft I-PER
voting O
_other_ I-ORG
everyone O
USA I-MISC
Sofia I-ORG
incident O
El I-ORG
Cedric I-PER
abandoned O
fraud O
Oakland I-ORG
Slough I-ORG
Index I-MISC
Johansson I-PER
minimum O
Grozny I-LOC
run O
conservative O
V I-ORG
message O
5,000 O
unclear O
II I-MISC
Monica I-PER
Assembly I-ORG
sports O
response O
factor O
Milan I-PER
homer O
941 O
Philadelphia I-ORG
' I-MISC
Bratislava I-LOC
--- O
separatists O
pleased O
Agriculture O
OF I-MISC
weakening O
instead O
immediate O
FRANCISCO I-ORG
Yeltsin I-PER
Kubo I-PER
Portsmouth I-ORG
penalty O
Francisco I-LOC
early O
UAE I-LOC
into O
' I-ORG
trend O
FC I-ORG
onto O
oil O
signal O
it O
Coast I-ORG
Damascus I-LOC
computer O
Whittall I-PER
Of O
surge O
The I-MISC
Blacks I-ORG
after O
dated O
includes O
Chonan I-ORG
slightly O
pace O
BRUSSELS I-LOC
Johnson I-PER
serious O
movement O
meet O
Costas I-PER
imports O
Algeria I-ORG
report O
Syria I-LOC
seriously O
offer O
Bourlet I-PER
shipment O
Andreas I-PER
festival O
Antwerp I-LOC
Best O
negative O
Blackburn I-PER
Dole I-ORG
Juan I-LOC
rainfall O
JOHANNESBURG I-LOC
First O
Brandes I-PER
Rapid I-ORG
Frank I-PER
kidnapped O
joined O
107 O
active O
JOSE I-LOC
Major O
is I-MISC
Net I-MISC
At O
Caen I-ORG
specific O
gets O
check O
While O
whole O
AS O
SERIES O
Council I-ORG
Bistrita I-LOC
Community I-LOC
judicial O
consulate O
Now O
prison O
Pittsburgh I-LOC
previous O
these O
fighting O
allowed O
Opposition O
.... O
China I-ORG
heads O
Speaker O
clear O
continuing O
frost O
social O
Sox I-ORG
of I-PER
Nepali I-MISC
Movement I-ORG
certainly O
battle O
Day I-MISC
Wales I-LOC
relief O
GOLF I-MISC
Institute I-ORG
Unita I-ORG
union O
things O
mixed O
Played O
1996-08-27 O
Club I-ORG
pretty O
fears O
EPR I-ORG
violence O
Salim I-PER
star O
RUGBY I-MISC
see O
Peace I-MISC
demanding O
drugs O
Peter I-PER
1,500 O
Thorpe I-PER
WESTERN I-MISC
importance O
deputy O
Asked O
Reserve O
producers O
containing O
within O
Indian I-LOC
publicly O
15-11 O
debt O
According O
list O
year O
boss O
Lewis I-MISC
minority O
briefing O
North I-PER
Roberto I-PER
beyond O
jet O
interests O
meetings O
Law I-PER
transition O
shows O
faced O
local O
64 O
Agency I-ORG
Union I-ORG
republic O
dozen O
because O
government O
missed O
help O
boxes O
Leon I-ORG
leaders O
Marcelo I-PER
forecast O
Bremen I-ORG
number O
39 O
foot O
stable O
scene O
Angeles I-PER
owners O
Committee I-MISC
Yugoslav I-MISC
Brisbane I-ORG
absence O
Leeds I-ORG
2000 O
embassy O
William I-PER
rail O
attempt O
and O
Democracy I-ORG
Auckland I-ORG
Port I-ORG
Sir O
explosives O
board O
risk O
Fall O
tried O
Following O
Beirut I-LOC
Rwanda I-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
weekly O
officials O
shared O
International O
8.0 O
Several O
prayers O
East I-MISC
reduced O
bus O
Police O
Andrei I-PER
managed O
western O
lending O
Davies I-PER
Eddie I-PER
Wayne I-PER
did O
ties O
sending O
Indian I-ORG
returns O
Kucera I-PER
accord O
Jewish B-MISC
300 O
Atlanta I-LOC
situation O
Gary I-PER
bodies O
Pires I-PER
first O
travel O
Terry I-PER
residents O
pledged O
goals O
changing O
consumers O
mandate O
Martinez I-PER
accepted O
Helibor I-MISC
Affairs O
carrying O
11 O
PHILADELPHIA I-LOC
San I-LOC
Boardman I-PER
5-1 O
wins O
motor O
from O
Nantes I-ORG
returned O
cash O
Gluten O
crashed O
Rwandan B-MISC
War I-MISC
analyst O
Marlins I-ORG
95 O
3-0 O
Other O
snap O
God I-PER
dn O
Argentine I-MISC
mainly O
Stefano I-PER
Cuba I-LOC
Zurich I-LOC
Blackpool I-ORG
95 I-MISC
would O
Portugal I-LOC
Banespa I-ORG
278 O
By O
critics O
came O
N I-ORG
iron O
Somerset I-ORG
Albanian I-MISC
P O
my O
Clinton I-PER
involving O
moment O
Olivier I-PER
Park I-LOC
trying O
pitched O
cost O
dead O
free I-LOC
Mike I-PER
Florida I-ORG
late O
SYDNEY I-LOC
Zaire I-LOC
+1 O
including O
ADRs I-MISC
future O
candidate O
Prince I-LOC
rates O
Lakes I-MISC
Athletics I-ORG
wheat O
declined O
Canada I-ORG
are O
parent O
throughout O
collision O
6-2 O
agreement O
prosecutors O
remove O
Anders I-PER
.02 O
FRANKFURT I-LOC
Chemlon I-ORG
seedings O
added O
volume O
PREMIER O
aboard O
spokeswoman O
Maleeva I-PER
giant O
suspected O
Federal I-ORG
needed O
Enqvist I-PER
merely O
fans O
Tranmere I-ORG
defeated O
Kenneth I-PER
Kerkrade I-ORG
Bratislava I-ORG
LOUIS I-ORG
160 O
York I-ORG
Startup I-ORG
manager O
high O
wounds O
three-game O
CONFIRMED O
County I-LOC
46 O
de I-PER
Costa I-PER
Coast I-LOC
Wimbledon I-ORG
gives O
riyal O
setting O
C O
column O
CAIRO I-LOC
lap O
Soviet I-LOC
very O
attempts O
maker O
More O
Athens I-LOC
spot O
faster O
WARSAW I-LOC
Globo I-ORG
Tankan I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
monitoring O
Security O
MOODY O
Two O
Mexico I-ORG
SER O
Southampton I-LOC
drawn O
about O
WINS O
Sri I-LOC
McCarthy I-PER
50 O
hunt O
insurance O
birds O
available O
kept O
1996-08-28 O
demand O
able O
surrender O
arrived O
strategic O
irregularities O
beginning O
Spanish I-MISC
higher O
kilometre O
9 O
seek O
Third O
hold O
starts O
Interior I-ORG
Net O
Colchester I-LOC
administration O
11.00 O
Games I-ORG
Nicolas I-PER
Treaty I-MISC
coming O
February O
young O
muscle O
village O
ING I-ORG
Tigers I-ORG
MANCHESTER I-LOC
passengers O
310 O
JC I-ORG
makers O
Reform I-ORG
land O
Bucharest I-LOC
guards O
effectively O
Hamlet O
bottle O
, O
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ I-LOC
Gov O
Iran I-ORG
Frankfurt I-ORG
Gatwick I-LOC
Miller I-PER
bulk O
Red I-ORG
mostly O
winners O
Thomas I-PER
West I-ORG
Alexander I-PER
entered O
7. O
Eriksson I-PER
teams O
House I-ORG
SERIES I-MISC
settlements O
Egypt I-LOC
+301 O
van O
After O
twice O
other O
Res I-ORG
level O
commitment O
Some O
Wroclaw I-ORG
FOR O
boats O
decided O
Rio I-ORG
" O
matches O
civilian O
concrete O
MPs O
BRUSSELS I-MISC
less O
Business O
Detroit I-ORG
Islamic B-MISC
Javier I-PER
Lincoln I-PER
Williams I-ORG
unq O
Portsmouth I-LOC
stocks O
grand O
trader O
Ferreira I-PER
Office I-ORG
Maskhadov I-PER
acquire O
expect O
magazine I-ORG
H1 O
Japan I-ORG
Texas I-ORG
85 O
Teresa I-PER
explain O
LOS I-ORG
took O
serve O
Neths I-LOC
People O
Colorado I-ORG
1997 O
assets O
SOUTH I-MISC
Billy I-PER
drug O
LEAGUE O
.527 O
Middle I-MISC
affairs I-ORG
turnover O
red O
London I-MISC
distance O
title O
were O
859 O
Bridge I-LOC
states O
hearing O
58 O
towards O
banned O
It O
Salisbury I-PER
grounds O
disappointed O
job O
96 I-MISC
Parliament O
captured O
attend O
actions O
best O
law I-MISC
engine O
trends O
beef O
Alkmaar I-ORG
rebel O
poll O
Tauziat I-PER
57th O
American I-MISC
Amanda I-PER
15-7 O
billion O
nurses O
timetable O
friend O
equaliser O
Bastia I-ORG
24th O
atmosphere O
Doetinchem I-ORG
South I-MISC
nun O
30 O
exchange O
system O
getting O
Guzman I-PER
Radio I-ORG
Israeli I-MISC
Cannes I-ORG
intent O
Freiburg I-ORG
Huber I-PER
firm O
third O
must O
. I-LOC
A. I-PER
Marc I-PER
Security I-ORG
Akam I-PER
names O
US I-ORG
Roda I-ORG
SOUTH O
Colonna I-PER
owns O
GB O
Baker I-PER
The I-LOC
Kent I-ORG
LISBON I-LOC
Nelson I-PER
room O
SEC I-ORG
Seoul I-LOC
Belgian I-MISC
Woosnam I-PER
rights O
Cincinnati I-ORG
supporters O
according O
highway O
suits O
radio O
entire O
High I-ORG
newsroom O
municipal O
Gilbert I-PER
threatened O
east O
allow O
Borussia I-ORG
exile O
one-day O
42 O
reforms O
America I-ORG
Tokyo I-ORG
met O
La I-ORG
ever O
Gerhard I-PER
Huddersfield I-ORG
boycott O
Lee I-PER
league O
quake O
Algiers I-LOC
Toyota I-ORG
thin O
company O
Yellow I-MISC
tough O
MEXICO I-LOC
2,000 B-MISC
Reform I-MISC
youth O
Geneva I-LOC
failure O
People I-MISC
consensus O
handgun O
significant O
millions O
crowds O
Arab I-MISC
Jakarta I-LOC
Vacek I-PER
receive O
wants O
14. O
Aki I-ORG
Italy I-LOC
landing O
scores O
followed O
Atlantic I-LOC
Zurich I-ORG
Stephane I-PER
affair O
handling O
although O
Northern I-ORG
Lehman I-ORG
Ali I-PER
prices O
S. I-LOC
paint O
championship I-MISC
News I-ORG
leaving O
Waqar I-PER
killer O
MFS I-ORG
Sergi I-PER
due O
life O
Key I-PER
Queen O
small O
15-12 O
JYVASKYLA I-LOC
Thailand I-LOC
Lyon I-ORG
PAY O
J. I-PER
_other_ O
may O
Rangers I-ORG
Akram I-PER
Sunday O
SV I-ORG
yet O
pulp O
comments O
sweeping O
Saudi I-LOC
railway O
join O
KONG I-LOC
increasing O
lost O
stories O
Khartoum I-LOC
Gulf I-MISC
Preston I-LOC
we O
caps O
George I-ORG
Congress I-ORG
venue O
Aamir I-PER
says O
rise O
Dodgers I-ORG
Woodbridge I-PER
FIRST O
yen O
fly O
Hussein I-PER
Hamilton I-PER
World I-MISC
[ O
Tillstrom I-PER
COLORADO I-LOC
him O
Arminia I-ORG
Jana I-PER
Catholic I-MISC
seven O
) I-ORG
Haitai I-ORG
media O
appeared O
U.N. I-ORG
Republic I-LOC
California I-MISC
Kevin I-PER
70th O
Street I-LOC
lifted O
doubles O
Southern I-ORG
Leicester I-ORG
Chile I-LOC
II I-PER
Financial I-ORG
cent O
79 O
16. O
escaped O
Karol I-PER
Bossi I-PER
PUNR I-ORG
bad O
12. O
1986 O
starting O
coast O
Arab I-ORG
advertising O
Brazilian I-MISC
most O
extremely O
LOUIS I-LOC
being O
storm O
subject O
Arabs I-MISC
Madrid I-LOC
qualifier O
Naoko I-PER
Zimbabwe I-LOC
January O
offering O
campaign O
heavily O
Partizan I-ORG
stockpile O
allied O
members O
47th O
headquarters O
policies O
standing O
important O
Uganda I-LOC
Eight O
Leading O
profitable O
students O
4,000 O
telling O
ending O
great O
cattle O
completed O
ground O
D O
CARLSBAD I-LOC
sexual O
latest O
From O
decline O
counterpart O
ferry O
forced O
SCORES O
like O
Zastava I-ORG
Canberra I-ORG
success O
until O
lions O
280 O
54 O
improved O
you O
English I-MISC
News O
7-2 O
Jordanian I-ORG
Mikael I-PER
Los I-LOC
find O
Moin I-PER
BAGHDAD I-LOC
gold O
push O
Glamorgan I-ORG
Greens B-ORG
ago O
Financial I-MISC
inning O
slam O
operator O
Nelson I-LOC
McGrath I-PER
today O
Frenchman I-MISC
equal O
spending O
Lopez I-PER
span O
Data I-ORG
rules O
CHICAGO I-MISC
different O
faces O
roads O
2000 I-ORG
athletes O
Sale I-ORG
southeast O
letters O
death O
hands O
12-15 O
: O
crackdown O
intercepted O
Nathalie I-PER
Chechens I-MISC
beat O
hijacking O
titles O
6.0 O
Soccer O
still O
cold O
possible O
support O
replacement O
Second I-MISC
located O
narrow O
livestock O
Queen I-ORG
Netanyahu I-PER
ABC I-ORG
break O
named O
71 O
Six O
why O
East I-ORG
passenger O
program O
semifinalist O
Spot I-PER
34 O
Nicaraguan I-MISC
Chechen I-MISC
Headley I-PER
31 I-LOC
Leverkusen I-ORG
- O
comes O
when O
serving O
revised O
Chg O
Doncaster I-MISC
4-0 O
manage O
carried O
Jim I-PER
Rifkind I-PER
LATEST O
15-10 O
behind O
leader O
humanitarian O
dictator O
House I-LOC
fire O
One I-MISC
murder O
CALIFORNIA I-ORG
Linz I-ORG
61-2 O
envoy O
Milan I-LOC
husband O
Pakistani I-LOC
SOUTH I-ORG
Yankees I-ORG
paid O
White I-PER
Thai I-ORG
corporate O
Czech I-MISC
Twins I-ORG
Pedro I-PER
outbreak O
Nearly O
Aslan I-PER
Bridge I-ORG
steady O
Boston I-ORG
painted O
Aires I-ORG
abuse O
1995 O
Boer I-PER
RESEARCH O
Mother O
already O
Zabrze I-LOC
Alami I-PER
Kan I-LOC
interior O
two-day O
wanted O
ca O
St I-LOC
Roman I-MISC
Juppe I-PER
_Num_ I-ORG
flights O
Jonathan I-PER
KONG I-MISC
television O
week O
session O
11 I-MISC
lines O
dragged O
previously O
northeast O
stake O
mean O
bid O
Hamilton I-ORG
El I-PER
Bistrita I-ORG
Headingley I-LOC
searched O
remained O
investors O
he O
Wimbledon I-MISC
400 O
stepped O
personal O
10.5 O
candidates O
Bosnian I-ORG
Sharif I-PER
defending O
lose O
problem O
FROM O
spent O
Oklahoma I-LOC
evidence O
confident O
official O
to O
plantation O
Sandra I-PER
Halftime O
Rwandan I-MISC
auction O
School O
Russian I-ORG
Herbert I-PER
Lodz I-ORG
Arabia I-LOC
shutdown O
traded O
1-0 O
Java I-MISC
County I-ORG
smaller O
UEFA I-ORG
Sheffield I-ORG
Sharpe I-PER
man O
saying O
K. I-PER
nominated O
Date I-PER
climb O
at O
post O
bank I-ORG
else O
never O
Drew I-PER
heard O
killing O
Le I-ORG
isolated O
171 O
contact O
Sarajevo I-LOC
Northern I-LOC
Bill I-PER
effort O
denotes O
City I-LOC
Michelle I-PER
arms O
Andrew I-PER
MINNESOTA I-LOC
Prize I-MISC
electoral O
People I-LOC
Chechnya I-LOC
Phil I-PER
raising O
ran O
All I-ORG
McLaren I-ORG
hijackers O
Nancy I-ORG
James I-PER
Blind I-PER
II I-ORG
US I-LOC
on I-MISC
driving O
part O
blow O
Rotterdam I-ORG
Davis I-MISC
Groningen I-ORG
Ross I-PER
Seles I-PER
Sanchez I-PER
more O
Gloucestershire I-ORG
Algerian I-MISC
14 O
Trafford I-LOC
Sun I-PER
DE I-ORG
Star I-ORG
pass O
boat O
Saddam I-PER
leg O
Thompson I-PER
preferred O
16 I-ORG
Surrey I-LOC
Republican I-MISC
much O
If O
border O
With O
hot O
former O
181 O
Rodriguez I-PER
Christian I-PER
Convention I-MISC
Porto I-ORG
Group I-ORG
CLEVELAND I-ORG
61 O
O'Neal I-PER
war O
OFFICIAL I-ORG
police O
Euro I-MISC
Ministry O
figure O
Qualifier O
Blackburn I-ORG
Villeneuve I-PER
kidnapping O
deal O
attending O
No I-MISC
Sudan I-ORG
Rican I-ORG
Arequipa I-ORG
Dacom I-ORG
champions O
add O
eighth O
Puchon I-ORG
Three O
bureau O
2-1 O
replace O
Erik I-PER
World O
continues O
moved O
France I-ORG
Postal I-ORG
food O
wells O
fighters O
born O
crossing O
Brooks I-ORG
Tour I-MISC
Earlier O
Mapei I-ORG
Khan I-PER
, I-MISC
Schumacher I-PER
William I-LOC
quarter O
opposition O
elections O
painful O
Switzerland I-MISC
Ahmed I-PER
7-6 O
attention O
beating O
Weaver I-PER
placings O
thanks O
real O
Democratic I-MISC
Zealand I-LOC
the O
.469 O
Health I-ORG
BELGRADE I-LOC
they O
overs O
Graf I-PER
Golf I-MISC
overnight O
gains O
his O
taking O
AG I-ORG
World B-MISC
of I-LOC
div O
Mohamed I-PER
picture O
green O
's I-LOC
Slight I-PER
white O
reliever O
Liberia I-ORG
own O
parliament O
CITY I-LOC
minutes O
supported O
Jon I-PER
Saturday O
McEwen I-PER
theft O
through O
fast O
Durham I-ORG
bounce O
mayor O
inventories O
diplomatic O
Community O
bombing O
Moslems I-MISC
midfielder O
Dow I-MISC
work O
India I-MISC
Metz I-ORG
CDU I-ORG
ministers O
generally O
Svetlana I-PER
Dublin I-LOC
8,000 O
100 I-MISC
effects O
San I-MISC
Heeswijk I-PER
witnesses O
Mickelson I-PER
founded O
linking O
Buenos I-LOC
fuel O
dollar O
325 O
go O
group O
stole O
Corser I-PER
Bangladesh I-ORG
Oct O
values O
seen O
Wigan I-ORG
division I-MISC
afternoon O
behalf O
GRAND B-MISC
telling I-MISC
BSE I-MISC
Tuesday O
Namibia I-LOC
W. I-LOC
runs O
warned O
dropped O
Ulihrach I-PER
Yassin I-PER
times O
DATE O
PRIX I-MISC
begin O
Australian I-ORG
Bombay I-ORG
bond O
SUPER O
specified O
22 O
veteran O
house O
Monde I-MISC
final O
talk O
several O
department O
sent O
1996-08-23 O
Neuchatel I-ORG
Bombay I-LOC
Spring I-LOC
Martin I-PER
800 O
recorded O
Secretary O
drove O
virus O
contribute O
directly O
link O
protests O
Southend I-ORG
Merrill I-ORG
Hong I-PER
aiming O
Gold I-PER
Liverpool I-ORG
Nazi I-MISC
appearance O
] O
Collstrop I-ORG
farm O
Capiot I-PER
PLO I-ORG
near O
debate O
planning O
avoided O
happen O
n't O
.470 O
R. I-PER
Brown I-PER
75 O
High O
1948 O
landed O
Civil I-ORG
Securities I-ORG
U.S. I-LOC
& I-LOC
treatment O
operations O
negotiator O
citizen O
couple O
PRICE O
hotel O
ready O
products O
Oxford I-ORG
three O
coup O
Golf O
servants O
tonne O
Warsaw I-ORG
Malaysia I-LOC
major O
not O
halt O
which O
transport O
window O
maintained O
plays O
HOUSTON I-ORG
Chesterfield I-ORG
have O
Lewis I-PER
Vienna I-ORG
ball O
jump O
AZ I-ORG
headed O
determine O
Luis I-PER
Manchester I-LOC
play O
Mayfair I-PER
lifting O
recalled O
commanding O
G. I-PER
thrown O
PULPEX I-ORG
Most O
partly O
1992 O
116 O
SAN I-LOC
106 O
Lehman I-PER
; O
Adams I-PER
Dutch I-MISC
soccer O
Games I-PER
're O
Khan I-LOC
stated O
Army O
Prince I-PER
Ohio I-LOC
GMT I-MISC
sentiment O
possibly O
3 I-ORG
Bamerindus I-ORG
Jones I-PER
fund O
straight O
rating O
Wellman I-ORG
Beirut I-ORG
missing O
Gore I-PER
easy O
Gujral I-PER
Hill I-MISC
Richard I-PER
goal O
court O
mining O
hurdles O
Fowler I-PER
paedophile O
Union I-LOC
carry O
Old I-MISC
without O
Celsius I-MISC
lb O
per O
last O
TV O
friends O
wicket O
split O
independence O
light O
18 O
Shares O
Iranian I-MISC
Court I-ORG
Conchita I-PER
12th O
Singapore I-ORG
cover O
Austrian I-MISC
promised O
singles O
Guinea I-LOC
Dinamo I-ORG
Norwich I-ORG
view O
failed O
Craig I-PER
Price O
chance O
camp O
.496 O
Women I-MISC
Wednesday I-ORG
investment O
der I-PER
Key O
Brooks I-PER
OAKLAND I-ORG
programme O
software O
bullish O
Middle I-LOC
deposit O
vouch O
$ O
Scott I-PER
Angels I-ORG
membership O
better O
closing O
Kurdistan I-LOC
Paris I-PER
Islamic I-MISC
medal O
popular O
83rd O
65 O
Ruch I-PER
Lauck I-PER
Financial O
runner-up O
becoming O
colony O
partnership O
KV O
tour O
's I-MISC
Division I-ORG
Rohrabacher I-PER
security O
night O
Nepali I-ORG
4.0 O
federal O
38 O
Stoke I-ORG
Thursday O
People I-ORG
serie I-MISC
marketing O
Palestinian I-MISC
secret O
AFTER O
Price I-MISC
issues O
2001 O
Lancashire I-ORG
Democrat I-ORG
Grobbelaar I-PER
Journal I-ORG
any O
Nasdaq I-MISC
Sri I-MISC
cholesterol O
look O
Wisconsin I-LOC
confidence O
Breda I-ORG
( I-LOC
Kelly I-PER
Novotna I-PER
When O
Women O
listed O
power O
Industry O
Johan I-PER
directed O
Hasina I-PER
90th O
rising O
province O
Dec O
turn O
Interfax I-ORG
Gazprom I-ORG
Giles I-PER
P I-ORG
on O
/ I-ORG
District I-ORG
KANSAS I-ORG
firing O
written O
education O
London I-LOC
Smith I-PER
Banisadr I-PER
newspaper O
businessman O
Export O
gain O
chief-of-staff O
Jimmy I-PER
wages O
129 O
1. O
10 O
Office I-MISC
baby O
quit O
Medvedev I-PER
WORLD O
term O
goods O
Stevanin I-PER
use O
9. O
Barry I-PER
Under O
Liu I-PER
tests O
DE I-LOC
Guerrero I-LOC
reaching O
Cambridge I-ORG
Up O
Friday O
GPG I-ORG
Angels I-LOC
self-rule O
May I-PER
II O
van I-PER
Belgium I-LOC
Singer I-PER
over O
Wellman I-PER
backed O
do O
test O
Information O
blocked O
3-1 O
quiet O
Mexican I-MISC
Berger I-PER
capped O
noted O
MILWAUKEE I-LOC
prix O
Taibe I-ORG
FINAL O
Social I-ORG
partner O
Ukraine I-LOC
Summary O
1992 I-MISC
S&P I-ORG
fails O
acts O
bronze O
developments O
World I-ORG
accuracy O
consider O
Finance I-ORG
fourth O
documents O
Baltimore I-ORG
weapon O
6- O
results O
responsible O
effect O
1-1 O
IOC I-ORG
street O
French I-ORG
France I-LOC
Tendulkar I-PER
_other_ I-MISC
make O
analysts O
Surrey I-ORG
walking O
Island I-LOC
Bank O
RBI I-ORG
Switzerland I-LOC
Leicestershire I-ORG
ATLANTA I-ORG
Operating O
speed O
Anthony I-PER
Kaluwitharana I-PER
history O
Party I-ORG
SUPER B-MISC
Pol I-PER
Peru I-LOC
roubles O
loaded O
Carl I-PER
outcome O
ruled O
trafficking O
And O
medicine O
missionary O
associated O
Soccer I-ORG
Schalke I-ORG
+7095 O
Bulgaria I-LOC
by O
soldier O
double O
families O
Aki I-PER
neither O
fever O
Pauli I-ORG
Helens I-ORG
Afghanistan I-LOC
Indians I-ORG
Natalya I-PER
WESTERN I-LOC
La I-MISC
explained O
Yasser I-PER
Waugh I-PER
traffic O
population O
series O
RACING O
On O
aimed O
Insurance I-ORG
victims O
Nikkei I-MISC
Hungary I-ORG
Stock O
cooperation O
Erbakan I-PER
ensure O
strikers O
makes O
consumer O
laps O
secure O
Hurricane O
feed O
BUENOS I-LOC
12-year-old O
attempted O
apparently O
course O
Specter I-PER
championships O
years O
soldiers O
Mubarak I-PER
race O
scientist O
Brooke I-PER
long-term O
7.5 O
32 O
advanced O
developed O
Swiss I-ORG
West I-LOC
resign O
relations O
SEOUL I-LOC
happened O
admitted O
Northampton I-ORG
310 I-MISC
New O
Brann I-ORG
54th O
26 O
Government I-ORG
walked O
EASTERN I-MISC
second O
recover O
0-1 O
These O
either O
Amman I-LOC
Summaries O
Subaru I-MISC
walk O
brokers O
Total O
Haga I-PER
Kawasaki I-ORG
Mitchell I-PER
profit-taking O
day O
prime O
successive O
many O
Magnus I-PER
along O
elsewhere O
reserves O
Stuttgart I-ORG
Basque I-MISC
guerrilla O
Club O
Stephen I-PER
UNION I-ORG
Nations I-MISC
Bailey I-PER
Athens I-ORG
30,000 O
convention I-MISC
opening O
Corsica I-LOC
bourse O
minute O
Slam I-MISC
Serb I-MISC
Monday O
interest O
finding O
Lotte I-PER
leads O
complained O
prepared O
woman O
Karachi I-LOC
follow O
pts O
book O
quick O
DIEGO I-LOC
means O
diplomat O
Iranian I-LOC
European I-MISC
receiving O
defender O
news O
pills O
... O
85th O
Russia I-LOC
arriving O
ban O
Oldham I-ORG
North I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
Home I-ORG
1 I-MISC
tie O
2 I-MISC
Mostostal I-ORG
crop O
portfolio O
Allenby I-PER
purchase O
Bolton I-ORG
get O
import O
F O
definitely O
at I-ORG
86 O
show O
bat O
1996 O
Milwaukee I-ORG
header O
Reeve I-PER
TV I-ORG
picked O
crown O
NEC I-MISC
57 O
Rally I-ORG
matter O
Montgomerie I-PER
Sofia I-LOC
Court O
road O
figures O
Carlos I-PER
hitting O
instructions O
Playing O
retain O
percentage O
pair O
British I-LOC
Kabul I-LOC
might O
industrial O
inch O
200 O
material O
falling O
Football I-LOC
Eindhoven I-ORG
v O
rule O
full O
Stich I-PER
13th O
State I-ORG
California I-ORG
sentences O
.. O
impact O
Hong I-MISC
Columbia I-LOC
retailer O
Revenue O
Taipei I-LOC
worth O
girls O
neighbours O
Ford I-ORG
Scores O
ROUND O
packed O
Boston I-LOC
Legia I-ORG
badly O
weeks O
She O
sell O
true O
anniversary O
Wellington I-LOC
what O
Defence O
Bob I-PER
Islamist I-MISC
Scorers O
emerged O
stock O
pullout O
few O
Stadler I-ORG
improve O
Motorola I-ORG
Series I-MISC
activities O
Rabbani I-PER
negotiations O
3. O
belonging O
Dm I-MISC
far O
Hamburg I-LOC
offered O
Chairman O
Group O
Third I-MISC
Kurdish I-ORG
Brunswijk I-PER
Edwards I-PER
stopped O
Wells I-LOC
State I-LOC
56th O
Botham I-PER
looking O
capital O
ask O
chances O
Virginia I-LOC
gained O
FC O
Kennedy I-PER
while O
Vermont I-LOC
operation O
Wilson I-PER
4.4 O
Best I-ORG
tries O
yr O
/ O
National I-LOC
wife O
calls O
Iraq I-LOC
systems O
and I-ORG
Kabul I-ORG
nil O
Match O
Dean I-PER
confirmed O
leadership O
guerrillas O
Islamists I-MISC
Cardinals I-ORG
MOTOR O
spokesman O
net O
Toyota I-MISC
Sauber I-ORG
Patricia I-PER
New I-MISC
place O
Bielefeld I-ORG
Caribbean I-LOC
125 O
sterling O
released O
scattered O
43 O
Ijaz I-PER
Queensland I-ORG
refunds O
Genoa I-ORG
asked O
600,000 O
potential O
losses O
FORECAST O
ambassador O
Christian I-MISC
LEADING O
heavy O
Central I-LOC
artillery O
party O
Celica I-MISC
Indonesian I-MISC
billions O
seems O
believe O
, I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
terms O
Last O
5-2 O
snapped O
unit O
result O
spend O
OB I-ORG
maximum O
surgery O
CLEVELAND I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
tennis O
stores O
executive O
aggregate O
BOSTON I-ORG
Rican I-MISC
Moscow I-ORG
Simon I-PER
90 O
Dole I-PER
General I-ORG
Irani I-PER
Hampshire I-LOC
Shanghai I-ORG
prayer O
October O
permission O
your O
PUK I-ORG
Gazeta I-ORG
gas O
Lotte I-ORG
liquidity O
200,000 O
dissidents O
letter O
payments O
reported O
Costa I-MISC
Levy I-PER
forces O
contents O
issue O
tree O
Cubs I-ORG
meets O
Grant I-PER
nations O
troops O
ICAC I-ORG
if O
multiple O
Sept O
White I-LOC
FRIENDLY O
kph O
CYCLING O
Hurricane I-ORG
Sao I-LOC
6-1 O
Gulf I-LOC
DEM I-MISC
proposal O
Louis I-PER
Treasury I-ORG
refugee O
Barcelona I-ORG
bpd O
Democrat I-MISC
Andre I-PER
further O
Krakow I-ORG
Bochum I-ORG
Berlex I-ORG
ONE-DAY O
Henman I-PER
camps O
Mullally I-PER
stayed O
draft O
routine O
Johannesburg I-LOC
Bank I-LOC
78 O
Aberdeen I-ORG
measures O
motion O
Democrats I-MISC
biggest O
COUNTY B-MISC
1987 O
Muster I-PER
treated O
389 O
apartheid O
formal O
the I-LOC
commander O
vehicle O
KONG I-ORG
film O
Sydney I-ORG
edge O
Times I-ORG
Reds I-ORG
SK I-ORG
religious O
Bordeaux I-ORG
postponed O
example O
ZIMBABWE I-LOC
112 O
Colchester I-ORG
expressed O
doubt O
Korda I-PER
hours O
de I-LOC
Leon I-PER
Birmingham I-ORG
health O
Takeda I-PER
Cooperation I-ORG
Sales O
representatives O
interim O
boxcar O
usual O
SPD B-ORG
STANDINGS O
broken O
Foreign O
Brazil I-LOC
Austria I-LOC
rather O
strategy O
ordered O
CUP I-MISC
Norway I-LOC
Spain I-ORG
Sun I-ORG
US$ I-MISC
community O
churches O
intensive O
Edouard I-PER
mind O
decisive O
Public I-LOC
Palace I-ORG
match O
Four I-ORG
SEATTLE I-ORG
recently O
Cocu I-PER
High I-LOC
One I-ORG
team O
buyers O
Fischler I-PER
tense O
) I-PER
rated O
Kim I-PER
Dealers I-ORG
_other_ I-PER
For O
always O
OPEN I-MISC
Turkey I-LOC
reporters O
criminal O
Add O
otherwise O
gunman O
Brisbane I-LOC
Fredericks I-PER
Rios I-PER
Dublin I-ORG
in O
Max I-PER
Reuters I-ORG
Cologne I-LOC
waste O
GOLF I-LOC
organisations O
train O
Ferguson I-PER
representing O
George I-PER
Fernandez I-PER
Industry I-ORG
university O
printed O
exact O
Russian I-LOC
Post I-PER
and I-MISC
unseeded O
Budapest I-LOC
say O
also O
construction O
But O
Lebanon I-LOC
none O
EUROPEAN I-MISC
Sierra I-ORG
Swansea I-ORG
all O
Houston I-PER
enough O
Seven I-MISC
Spring I-PER
published O
Kurdistan I-ORG
dealers O
Greek I-MISC
role O
clause O
threw O
MaliVai I-PER
Ten O
School I-ORG
Van I-LOC
vs. O
OM I-ORG
37 O
Toronto I-ORG
Steve I-PER
bids O
Kong I-MISC
growth O
homers O
cycling O
Council I-MISC
Tom I-PER
command O
SUMMARIES O
described O
drew O
81 O
8520 O
displayed O
North I-MISC
Suwon I-ORG
NETHERLANDS I-MISC
Joyce I-PER
dollars O
reduce O
our O
82 O
Missionaries I-ORG
Akron I-ORG
Vermont I-ORG
champion O
plant O
stand O
Gingrich I-PER
winter O
FLORIDA I-LOC
Essex I-LOC
Hashimoto I-PER
Raymond I-PER
Zinzan I-PER
JAKARTA I-LOC
south O
trial O
Crawley I-PER
blame O
civil O
Pirates I-ORG
spinal O
organised O
Old O
positive O
working O
Fox I-PER
kingdom O
Rally I-MISC
seconds O
played O
announcement O
similar O
votes O
nuclear O
5.5 O
Election I-ORG
rand O
fled O
style O
Stansted I-LOC
Munich I-LOC
required O
just O
33 O
formed O
begins O
in I-ORG
chief O
G O
planned O
Thai I-MISC
big O
large O
closes O
New I-ORG
Knight I-PER
Men O
yards O
Willem I-ORG
All I-MISC
eastern O
boost O
tourist O
Manchester I-ORG
language O
the I-PER
probe O
extended O
cars O
determined O
Lynch I-ORG
Netherlands I-MISC
base O
houses O
Basuki I-PER
Washington I-PER
refugees O
telephone O
Armstrong I-PER
money O
There O
LAKES I-MISC
minister O
Dick I-PER
face O
miss O
larger O
Air I-ORG
Islamic I-ORG
Howard I-PER
450,000 O
= O
Republicans I-MISC
Grand B-MISC
abuses O
create O
winds O
accords O
Division I-MISC
Davenport I-PER
capacity O
P. I-PER
seeded O
CAPS O
Centre O
1980s O
put O
accompanied O
no I-MISC
Abdul I-PER
Sittard I-ORG
RUGBY I-ORG
noon O
1996-08-26 O
Cup B-MISC
son O
sealed O
referendum O
Chelsea I-ORG
governor O
Ballanger I-PER
Subaru I-ORG
Jan I-PER
politics O
_other_ B-MISC
region O
separatist O
single O
Latvia I-LOC
Reading I-ORG
huge O
47 O
Kocinski I-PER
property O
Emnid I-ORG
limited O
blamed O
Ltd I-ORG
10th O
D. I-PER
north I-LOC
Frankie I-PER
Bedie I-PER
career O
Young I-ORG
CANADIAN I-MISC
Olympics I-MISC
Europe I-LOC
Togo I-LOC
WASHINGTON I-LOC
stay O
Jayasuriya I-PER
AUG O
Ruutel I-PER
wo O
Yugoslavia I-LOC
Co I-ORG
New I-LOC
subsidiary O
Irish I-MISC
squad O
0 O
International I-ORG
3.2 O
commentary O
voter O
Denmark I-LOC
need O
About O
Thousands O
Royal I-LOC
past O
overseas O
Ligier I-ORG
Edwards I-ORG
COLORADO I-ORG
six O
newsdesk O
child O
ninth O
Christopher I-PER
180 O
PDS B-ORG
spying O
Alaska I-LOC
Miami I-LOC
Amsterdam I-ORG
how O
slight O
Princess O
Lebed I-PER
Dhaka I-LOC
Tim I-PER
mm O
Wheat I-ORG
Pete I-PER
good O
Agriculture I-ORG
position O
was O
66 O
CENTRAL I-MISC
Stewart I-PER
Hampshire I-ORG
CPI O
schedule O
pct O
Saudi I-ORG
score O
Preston I-ORG
French I-MISC
opponents O
2-0 O
Southern I-MISC
jobs O
attack O
task O
Hamlet I-MISC
Anne I-PER
garden O
Spaniard I-MISC
ordering O
Russian I-MISC
Dan I-ORG
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ O
Mika I-PER
6-5 O
Government O
once O
immediately O
Tamils I-MISC
assessment O
bureau I-ORG
estimate O
Union O
What O
helped O
Open I-MISC
short O
RTRS I-ORG
include O
as O
Colombia I-ORG
Sao I-ORG
controlled O
barter O
Rugby I-ORG
airport O
posted O
Black I-PER
Ferrari I-ORG
parts O
Batistuta I-PER
Astros I-ORG
crime O
comment O
disarmament O
Koerts I-PER
Ata-ur-Rehman I-PER
Indians I-MISC
prospect O
pesetas O
Inc. I-ORG
range O
My I-MISC
possibility O
35th O
registration O
National I-MISC
unc O
1/2 O
entering O
communications O
law O
Commercial O
Linford I-PER
bread O
bank O
discuss O
filed O
taxi O
diplomats O
qualified O
_allCaps_ I-PER
control O
Pacific I-ORG
move O
hits O
Serbian I-MISC
Peace O
attended O
First I-ORG
MON O
1 I-ORG
received O
Hungary I-LOC
Seoul I-ORG
doctors O
Nancy I-PER
First I-MISC
given O
Rovers I-ORG
Olympic I-MISC
passed O
Todd I-PER
interview O
preliminary O
unless O
Over O
Baghdad I-LOC
Hassan I-PER
balls O
Socialist O
Hyundai I-ORG
Charity I-ORG
3-6 O
Slovak I-MISC
Kiev I-LOC
Eefje I-PER
striker O
clocked O
Expos I-ORG
Greg I-PER
CPI I-MISC
% O
opinion O
lawyer O
Committee I-ORG
80th O
budget O
Angeles I-ORG
MONDAY O
reimbursement O
acres O
collided O
Monaco I-LOC
fellow O
friendly O
S. I-PER
concern O
5/8 O
cotton O
Judith I-PER
Malta I-LOC
short-term O
23 O
Revolutionary I-ORG
Surabaya I-LOC
Prince O
Jul O
perhaps O
States I-LOC
continued O
CALIFORNIA I-LOC
laws O
TO O
opposed O
forecasts O
1996-08-22 O
postponement O
Louis I-ORG
Red I-MISC
drive O
human O
sixth O
ST I-LOC
assembly O
Burundi I-LOC
two-run O
Allen I-PER
guilty O
Corporation I-ORG
The I-ORG
15-6 O
caught O
step O
Jorge I-PER
groups O
Mujtaba I-PER
going O
almost O
Essex I-ORG
target O
Names I-MISC
resume O
BONN I-LOC
MILAN I-ORG
July O
KDP I-ORG
_Num_ O
Leicester I-LOC
's O
weak O
city O
scandal O
Maria I-PER
74 O
investigating O
1949 O
David I-PER
garlic O
September O
expected O
Hong I-LOC
hour O
Orioles I-ORG
some O
metres O
Jones I-MISC
County I-MISC
custody O
69 O
feel O
magazines O
no O
Boris I-PER
SUMMARY O
1,000 I-MISC
Van I-ORG
St I-ORG
said O
ceasefire O
difference O
1995/96 O
coast I-LOC
pressure O
loans O
Daewoo I-ORG
Young I-PER
BUDAPEST I-LOC
peso O
centre O
6.5 O
OJ O
Romanian I-ORG
Cleveland I-ORG
yuan O
ETA I-ORG
Board I-ORG
resolution O
Airways O
15,000 O
Banharn I-PER
its O
pulled O
people O
THURSDAY O
genocide O
Jamaica I-LOC
4-3 O
vehicles I-ORG
radical O
Worcestershire I-ORG
Moxon I-PER
strongly O
fob O
Kong I-LOC
declared O
Russell I-PER
TOTAL O
LANKA I-LOC
Canberra I-LOC
planes O
Minnesota I-LOC
legal O
hoped O
prompt O
British I-MISC
Ian I-PER
McLaren I-MISC
suspects O
tabulate O
everything O
Sohail I-PER
Moldova I-LOC
1993 O
SRI I-LOC
BUCHAREST I-LOC
Edgar I-PER
Inc I-ORG
tension O
LG I-ORG
Albert I-PER
victory O
Chief O
Tass I-ORG
via O
gross O
DIEGO I-ORG
rural O
Jordan I-PER
In O
researchers O
Her O
skilled O
Belgrade I-ORG
Bangkok I-LOC
1996-08-25 O
15th O
player O
Battle I-MISC
kills O
gun O
County B-MISC
Business I-ORG
crude O
Southampton I-ORG
Cyprus I-ORG
RALLY I-MISC
condition O
Central I-ORG
RECORD O
premier O
auctions O
Arthur I-ORG
vowed O
Internet I-ORG
sentenced O
Larnaca I-ORG
country O
bonds O
expects O
freight O
yesterday O
Jerusalem I-LOC
Queen I-LOC
questioned O
Melbourne I-LOC
monitors O
space O
TOKYO I-LOC
Golf I-PER
AMERICAN I-MISC
266 O
Oncins I-PER
threatening O
invitation O
places O
walkover O
Havre I-ORG
quickly O
killed O
n't I-MISC
Shr O
Rubin I-PER
Australia I-ORG
waiting O
African I-MISC
Jan O
evening O
Ferrigato I-PER
sparked O
Dhaka I-ORG
Sampras I-PER
DRAW O
KANSAS I-LOC
Hungarian I-MISC
praised O
supply O
tabulated O
acquisition O
Boston I-PER
election O
Belarus I-LOC
does O
Wolf I-PER
pinch-hitter O
Royal I-ORG
drought O
changed O
lack O
Dortmund I-ORG
Convention I-ORG
176 O
eventually O
individual O
morning O
car O
Medical O
Power I-ORG
relatively O
Biogen I-ORG
Human O
SUPER I-MISC
even O
ransom O
rain O
independent O
Chris I-PER
No O
putting O
Ischinger I-PER
aircraft O
Ruch I-ORG
Research O
allegations O
income O
Tamil I-MISC
NOTES O
off O
arrangements O
Sion I-ORG
Front I-ORG
NZ I-LOC
protest O
where O
Paul I-PER
Doboj I-LOC
DIVISION O
Index O
Juha I-PER
No I-ORG
Polish I-MISC
live O
Max O
has O
world O
One O
Ipswich I-ORG
_allCaps_ I-ORG
398 O
effective O
contest O
Christie I-PER
DIV O
introduced O
Palkhivala I-PER
Virginia I-PER
Taleban I-MISC
Arkansas I-LOC
Sale O
criticised O
Algeria I-LOC
gathering O
32.0 O
and I-LOC
strikeouts O
PCT O
November O
daily O
attributable O
17 O
Indonesian I-ORG
Czech I-LOC
Did O
Open O
Damon I-PER
try O
Anton I-PER
wage O
cup O
end O
NATIONS I-ORG
CHAMPIONSHIP I-MISC
U.S I-LOC
Taibe I-LOC
cargoes O
220 O
m O
hope O
demanded O
3-2 O
grew O
Two I-MISC
form O
Palace I-LOC
Florence I-PER
TOUR I-MISC
Albania I-LOC
Arafat I-PER
pitch O
route O
Valletta I-ORG
itself O
Q2 O
CAC-40 I-MISC
Frederic I-PER
claimed O
LEAGUE I-MISC
Hussain I-PER
fun O
Grand O
Carter I-PER
achieve O
1 O
62 O
Dundee I-ORG
Atlanta I-ORG
marijuana O
1-6 O
OSCE I-ORG
up O
SOFIA I-LOC
incumbent O
held O
privatization O
selected O
changes O
oppose O
11-6 O
Black O
+3 O
Atlanta B-MISC
Peace I-LOC
' O
benefit O
newspapers O
Miss I-ORG
TOSHIBA I-MISC
consecutive O
Arthur I-PER
pull O
7-3 O
value O
yield O
reveal O
Grasshoppers I-ORG
Yemen I-LOC
vote O
Rwanda I-LOC
Maoist I-MISC
Bernd I-PER
majors O
links O
Egyptian I-MISC
illness O
a O
showed O
LME I-ORG
Ballybunion I-ORG
doing O
Moura I-PER
is O
victim O
Prague I-ORG
accused O
addressed O
residence O
suicide O
Ssangbangwool I-ORG
danger O
Jakarta I-ORG
recovery O
areas O
Gephardt I-PER
key O
dark O
OF O
proposals O
Only O
Ferrari I-MISC
Sosa I-PER
Vicario I-PER
Chang I-PER
noise O
F.C. I-ORG
football O
Korean I-MISC
begun O
factors O
infusion O
militants O
truck O
statement O
protesters O
total O
USDA I-ORG
Major I-MISC
points O
120 O
Fairbrother I-PER
San I-ORG
11th O
1988 O
Van O
Doctors O
first-round O
BANGKOK I-LOC
Evert I-PER
National I-ORG
11. O
1999 O
cow O
Broadhurst I-PER
Walker I-PER
Pacific I-LOC
.504 O
Klinsmann I-PER
cargo O
strike O
hurt O
PRESS O
5. O
As O
Ken I-PER
Bonds I-ORG
palace O
sees O
CINCINNATI I-ORG
Cea I-PER
African I-LOC
Villa I-ORG
Birmingham I-LOC
abduction O
Rostock I-ORG
TVM I-ORG
La I-LOC
Graham I-PER
showers O
Netherlands I-LOC
farms O
Port O
O'Brien I-PER
return O
Saskatchewan I-LOC
DETROIT I-ORG
Ministry I-ORG
Saudi I-MISC
finds O
area O
table O
0-0 O
qualifying O
holes O
age O
Avonex I-MISC
Patriotic I-ORG
Vladimir I-PER
playing O
TITLE O
Dutroux I-PER
Escort I-MISC
send O
association O
airports O
Taylor I-PER
FRENCH I-MISC
numbers O
LAST O
London I-ORG
Gajdos I-PER
Charlton I-ORG
size O
particularly O
COUNTY I-MISC
HELSINKI I-LOC
N.J. I-LOC
bringing O
Jordan I-ORG
Twente I-ORG
Louis I-LOC
nationalist O
sentence O
details O
Shane I-PER
Supreme O
another O
below O
record O
.466 O
WIN O
dealer O
knew O
Jason I-PER
Alesi I-PER
charged O
tournament O
Vatican I-LOC
now O
Havre I-LOC
Coetzer I-PER
1996/97 O
holds O
Feyenoord I-ORG
THE O
COLOMBO I-LOC
Civil O
Ivanisevic I-PER
briefly O
communist O
disease O
nomination O
fours O
YEAR-AGO O
Universe I-ORG
unknown O
Date O
Israel I-ORG
outstanding O
ON O
Australia I-LOC
Bulgarian I-MISC
imposed O
Hong I-ORG
king O
bilateral O
Goran I-PER
THIRD O
trained O
so O
force O
again O
Romanian I-MISC
Rosati I-PER
87 O
Lanka I-LOC
Commissioner O
Sierra I-LOC
555 O
Alberto I-PER
UEFA I-MISC
've O
territory O
1991 O
jailed O
units O
fairly O
period O
56 O
tested O
Armed O
Turkish I-MISC
21st I-MISC
northern O
United I-ORG
had O
won O
Dividend O
Federation I-LOC
Graafschap I-ORG
+31 O
told O
church O
remote O
confirm O
Kandahar I-LOC
representative O
Masterkova I-PER
Hearts I-ORG
driver O
Ford I-MISC
Queensland I-LOC
Breda I-LOC
Bahamas I-LOC
trouble O
Johnson I-LOC
Standings O
Nepal I-ORG
hostages O
presidency O
Gough I-PER
selling O
distribution O
impossible O
Volendam I-ORG
Slovenia I-LOC
Montreal I-ORG
establish O
CRICKET O
LOS I-LOC
worldwide O
Luxembourg I-LOC
Tommy I-PER
fair O
4-95 O
women O
additional O
Gingrich I-ORG
Zimbabwe I-ORG
GRAND O
DHAKA I-LOC
199 O
foreigners O
Brush I-ORG
bought O
Petra I-ORG
freedom O
Rosset I-PER
Series O
looked O
Association I-ORG
answer O
N. I-PER
Kansas I-ORG
Nilis I-PER
bomb O
review O
others O
Lamm I-PER
Armed I-ORG
King I-PER
increase O
shed O
59th O
State O
stance O
hospital I-LOC
Capital I-ORG
Also O
Vale I-PER
reputation O
Rennes I-ORG
lives O
rains O
act O
ATHENS I-LOC
German I-ORG
become O
Thomson I-ORG
regarding O
mainland O
They O
Mutola I-PER
Sparta I-ORG
Plymouth I-ORG
Weld I-PER
club O
signs O
Chicago I-ORG
nine O
Magdalena I-PER
European I-ORG
Result O
Rafter I-PER
gestures O
visiting O
seat O
Senate I-ORG
MSV I-ORG
rider O
cleared O
Leeds I-MISC
new O
pushed O
under O
Medicare I-MISC
Irina I-PER
repeatedly O
rallied O
appeal O
Maybe O
Sarah I-PER
allocated O
appear O
Strasbourg I-ORG
Second O
States I-ORG
I O
W. I-PER
Linz I-LOC
too O
sector O
Faulding I-ORG
Christopher I-LOC
information O
India I-ORG
assault O
Brazil I-ORG
km O
rest O
holiday O
finally O
Yihye I-PER
signed O
think O
jewelry O
decision O
BASEBALL O
Alan I-PER
defeat O
let O
for I-MISC
lei O
found O
Kurd I-MISC
west O
died O
crash O
13 O
employee O
Just O
Jewish I-MISC
Sheffield I-PER
faction O
Ivorian I-MISC
polls O
Tapie I-PER
kill O
unable O
Meri I-PER
cut O
CLASSIC I-MISC
FRANCISCO I-LOC
Winners O
gone O
Frankfurt I-LOC
? O
Mohammad I-PER
Palmans I-ORG
exiled O
Field I-LOC
parliamentary O
JERUSALEM I-LOC
toward O
executed O
Singapore I-LOC
should O
Polonia I-ORG
Maria I-LOC
.500 O
exclusive O
Costa I-ORG
successful O
acting O
ACC I-ORG
bed O
delegates O
Seattle I-LOC
Liam I-PER
opens O
margins O
BALTIMORE I-ORG
surplus O
6. O
launch O
19th O
streak O
fight O
reason O
Conference I-ORG
me O
existing O
keep O
rescued O
Saskatchewan I-ORG
start O
cases O
Bayern I-ORG
estimated O
foreign O
Hingis I-PER
Royal I-PER
ALERT O
York I-LOC
Duesseldorf I-ORG
Colombia I-LOC
one O
fiscal O
Chesterfield I-LOC
every O
two O
John I-PER
shareholders O
owned O
finished O
making O
growing O
outperform O
PKK I-ORG
deficit O
line O
failing O
6-0 O
HONG I-MISC
share O
note O
Seattle I-ORG
then O
express O
27 O
Extras O
those O
50,000 O
quite O
BALTIMORE I-LOC
Dayton I-LOC
box O
halftime O
cool O
Kohl I-PER
progress O
seasons O
Traders O
Vienna I-LOC
2 O
162 O
Sydney I-LOC
open O
charge O
DUBAI I-LOC
she O
Gilbertson I-PER
boosted O
but O
profits O
Zhirinovsky I-PER
talks O
TIRANA I-LOC
sharply O
satisfied O
44 O
state O
Classic I-MISC
Data O
governments O
bln O
demands O
parents O
win O
embargo O
Machado I-PER
attacks O
involves O
discussions O
Kenya I-LOC
propaganda O
Former I-LOC
Irish I-ORG
boy O
hog O
Canadian I-MISC
staged O
reached O
64th O
Atlantic I-ORG
( O
Carlos I-LOC
Tennis O
four-day O
b O
article O
press O
Commander O
Prague I-LOC
spoke O
Japan I-LOC
That O
right-wing O
fifth O
motor I-ORG
Monaco I-ORG
Karina I-PER
Systems I-ORG
monthly O
protection O
Nijmegen I-ORG
England I-LOC
glass O
Anyang I-ORG
Ajax I-ORG
7.0 O
Marco I-PER
NATIONAL O
mine O
mission O
52 O
Bayer I-ORG
Prime O
Wall I-PER
FDP B-ORG
grain O
bright O
Department I-ORG
DETROIT I-LOC
save O
Romania I-LOC
HONG I-LOC
Thomson I-PER
Germany I-ORG
present O
Hutu I-MISC
ACTUAL O
voted O
Barnsley I-ORG
understanding O
Tyrrell I-ORG
WEDNESDAY O
rupiah O
Michael I-PER
unfortunate O
Adrian I-PER
raised O
Karlsruhe I-ORG
Conference I-MISC
33rd O
'm O
'll O
balance O
_Num_ I-MISC
GDP O
activity O
abroad O
water O
closed O
Fiorentina I-ORG
Sporting I-ORG
Polonia I-PER
Tehran I-LOC
Wasim I-PER
Kimiko I-PER
funds O
home O
36 O
calling O
Cardiff I-LOC
AMSTERDAM I-LOC
highlights O
considering O
defence O
Press I-ORG
mark O
TUESDAY O
giving O
Dutch I-ORG
Spot O
tanks O
West I-PER
Bromwich I-ORG
themselves O
EPS O
Afghan I-MISC
Street O
Enschede I-ORG
commission O
Bristol I-LOC
private O
Bonilla I-PER
Price I-PER
person O
product O
children O
bushel O
Nepal I-LOC
MAJOR I-MISC
Post I-ORG
Soyoil O
Social I-MISC
aide O
Houston I-LOC
1.2 O
among O
Middlesbrough I-ORG
editorial O
finals O
announce O
acquired O
Wells I-PER
4-6 O
futures O
Tang I-PER
Mother I-LOC
Fortuna I-ORG
Cairo I-LOC
Fax O
personnel O
Health O
Italian I-MISC
83 O
Rocca I-PER
economy O
shot O
quarterly O
Andrea I-PER
extra O
GERMAN I-MISC
visited O
word O
heart O
America I-LOC
SPLA I-ORG
compensation O
travelling O
right O
truce O
backing O
contracts O
paper O
terrorism O
L I-ORG
Giants I-ORG
PHILADELPHIA I-ORG
Trade O
Winners I-MISC
Park I-ORG
venture O
medallist O
Black I-LOC
towns O
Lanusse I-PER
4-2 O
established O
Street I-ORG
Younis I-PER
performance O
NEC I-ORG
premium O
winners I-MISC
Labour I-ORG
business O
ministry O
cricket O
status O
Cofinec I-ORG
Their O
Island I-PER
decree O
Hamburg I-ORG
Minnesota I-ORG
Hamas I-ORG
TENNIS O
TEST O
penalties O
greatest O
river O
Aug O
mln O
AND I-ORG
equipment O
shortly O
Yorkshire I-ORG
civilians O
Bohdan I-PER
4. O
Petr I-PER
Australia I-MISC
June O
decisions O
9/16 O
Johnny I-PER
U.S. I-ORG
maintain O
shown O
FLORIDA I-ORG
airliner O
regions O
Deputy O
sometimes O
Africa I-MISC
striking O
White I-ORG
riots O
internal O
Allenby I-LOC
Stenning I-PER
Washington I-LOC
with O
RALLY O
despite O
60th O
blown O
buying O
All O
agreed O
prompted O
Roosevelt I-PER
months O
outside O
politician O
flow O
Police I-ORG
King O
fatal O
credit O
Kan I-PER
JERUSALEM I-ORG
rally O
elect O
truth O
for O
tender O
109 O
Amoco I-ORG
five-run O
endorse O
Detroit I-LOC
allowing O
YORK I-LOC
across O
least O
Los I-MISC
NAC I-ORG
intended O
Massachusetts I-ORG
revenues O
Gloria I-PER
Iraqis I-MISC
40 O
militia O
tied O
Wolf I-LOC
Rose I-PER
nearly O
Amsterdam I-LOC
junior O
alleged O
vehicles O
safety O
radio I-ORG
both O
Oxford I-LOC
suspect O
vs O
produced O
GRAND I-MISC
Christian I-ORG
END O
Many O
Liberia I-LOC
allegedly O
Patrick I-PER
illegal O
Werder I-ORG
Hansa I-ORG
amnesty O
Angel I-PER
Since O
animal O
serie O
strong O
Serbs I-MISC
field O
hijacked O
keeping O
Universe I-MISC
76 I-MISC
deny O
labour O
currency O
expectations O
riding O
OJ I-ORG
Mideast I-LOC
Basque I-LOC
Iraqi I-MISC
Hutu B-MISC
destitute O
journalists O
cement O
flying O
93 O
Ireland I-LOC
de O
unchanged O
5-7 O
DIVISION I-MISC
piece O
Lithuania I-LOC
Stuttgart I-LOC
lived O
Mexican I-ORG
violations O
model O
Analysts O
tax O
Warburg I-ORG
France I-MISC
India I-LOC
kidnappers O
Brady I-PER
reopened O
kuna O
policy O
High B-LOC
quality O
67 O
28 O
Britain I-LOC
delayed O
midnight O
'S I-ORG
.538 O
wounded O
only O
Ambassador O
stronger O
Super I-MISC
brought O
fewer O
10-15 O
Supreme I-ORG
idea O
farmers O
special O
college O
promoted O
Gencor I-ORG
soybeans O
Rotterdam I-LOC
Sudanese I-MISC
affairs O
TIMES O
Braves I-ORG
Nobel I-MISC
Philadelphia I-LOC
earlier O
University I-ORG
20,000 O
Polish I-ORG
Corp. I-ORG
cents O
Japanese I-MISC
Chorzow I-LOC
ENGLISH I-MISC
Human I-ORG
injuries O
warning O
holders O
Chelsea I-PER
agenda O
Chamorro I-PER
Auckland I-LOC
percent O
Social O
Saeed I-PER
post-Soviet I-MISC
6-4 O
suit O
inches O
Alaska I-ORG
Necmettin I-PER
injury O
Power I-PER
taken O
die O
Export I-ORG
McCarthy I-ORG
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ B-MISC
projects O
defenders O
office O
48 O
sexually O
warrants O
_allCaps_ I-MISC
filled O
coalition O
Texas I-LOC
53 O
: I-MISC
Zenith I-ORG
sanctions O
OF I-LOC
fields O
overall O
His O
threat O
1980 O
head O
stop O
wing O
Popov I-PER
Los I-ORG
Petroleum I-ORG
SEATTLE I-LOC
Khmer I-ORG
Phan I-PER
appointed O
majority O
ordinary O
side O
Park I-PER
3.5 O
Milan I-ORG
study O
against I-MISC
Phillies I-ORG
index O
Dan I-PER
strikes O
1,000 O
Tommi I-PER
Port I-LOC
December O
9373-1800 O
date O
RBI I-MISC
Moody I-ORG
pound O
STAGE O
Team I-ORG
3 O
TORONTO I-LOC
Linhart I-PER
chains O
40,000 O
Brady I-MISC
medical O
Lens I-ORG
highly O
lower O
done O
HOUSTON I-LOC
_allCaps_ B-LOC
thought O
Arch I-ORG
Plc I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
factions O
GOLF O
58th O
Four I-MISC
having O
activists O
20 O
Lankan I-MISC
Kontogiannis I-PER
negotiated O
Asif I-PER
Auxerre I-ORG
PSV I-ORG
load O
largest O
Cuban I-MISC
postpone O
re-election O
long O
stood O
1996-08-21 O
General O
Hatoyama I-PER
sale O
Corp I-ORG
Roosevelt I-LOC
golf O
materials O
choice O
wrote O
1860 I-ORG
PSG I-ORG
Hamilton I-LOC
V. I-PER
AND O
c O
) O
GENEVA I-LOC
signing O
Waalwijk I-ORG
known O
aggressive O
ISS I-ORG
Benjamin I-PER
before O
Roger I-PER
difficulties O
Nottingham I-ORG
posts O
fishermen O
renewed O
advantage O
federation O
improvement O
) I-LOC
aviation O
Civil I-MISC
guilders O
output O
Perry I-PER
National O
Dynamo I-ORG
Colin I-PER
Two I-ORG
212-859-1650 O
version O
OUT O
Seven O
UK I-ORG
seventh O
formally O
body O
investigation O
order O
weather O
aims O
Melissa I-PER
against O
Pakistani I-MISC
the I-MISC
V O
4.0 I-MISC
HONG I-ORG
stage O
900 O
PITTSBURGH I-LOC
Hill I-PER
77 O
Gold O
spring O
Pinas I-PER
production O
Shanghai I-LOC
PARIS I-LOC
10,000 O
inside O
nor O
countries O
export O
10. O
nearby O
bowled O
cabinet O
know O
Bureau I-ORG
there O
whales O
Vitesse I-ORG
IVAC I-ORG
ENGLAND I-LOC
rare O
resignation O
Jose I-LOC
French I-LOC
District O
Weizman I-PER
concerns O
L O
engineering O
especially O
Sven I-PER
Wall I-ORG
worst O
volatility O
Fox I-ORG
Rangarajan I-PER
efforts O
sectors O
Philip I-PER
Colombo I-PER
Abu I-PER
affect O
Not O
market O
5.0 O
breaking O
each O
Croatian I-MISC
lift O
diverted O
Barbara I-LOC
suspended O
address O
U.S. I-MISC
Newcastle I-ORG
cross O
mate O
Houston I-ORG
announced O
competition O
politicians O
1996-08-24 O
Istanbul I-ORG
kerosene O
procedure O
trading O
scored O
of I-ORG
sheep O
meal O
Arsenal I-ORG
options O
15-9 O
plan O
3311812-4 O
contacts O
Kremlin I-LOC
Raith I-ORG
winning O
policemen O
north O
Current O
_containsDigitAndAlpha_ I-ORG
markets O
Paris I-ORG
follows O
industry O
par O
clearly O
doctor O
showing O
deposed O
Israel I-LOC
opened O
Spartak I-ORG
SCHEDULE O
margin O
come O
president O
deals O
prisoners O
pilot O
Makinen I-PER
Ibrahim I-PER
delivered O
widespread O
Reiffel I-PER
running O
MOODY I-ORG
WORLD I-MISC
helicopter O
account O
China I-LOC
finance O
Sachs I-ORG
'S O
